- ObjectiveID: 9901_0036_masterofthetempest
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 40.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest
  NpcDestinationId: 9919_MSQ_WardenScout
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_36
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_35 || 99D_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9901_0036_masterofthetempest_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_title"
  Description: "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: null
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: null
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : null
- ObjectiveID: 9901_0057_insoulinstone
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9901_0057_d_00_container_insoulinstone
  NpcDestinationId: 0717_Warden
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_57
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_56 || 99E_MSQ_11
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9901_0057_insoulinstone_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestReward_MSQFinale
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_objective_title"
  Description: "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9910_0057_insoulinstone_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: null
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: true
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : null
- ObjectiveID: 9910_0058_finallyexhale
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9910_0058_d_00_container_finallyexhale
  NpcDestinationId: 9905e_MSQ_Rima
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_58
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_57
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9910_0058_finallyexhale_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_title"
  Description: "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: null
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: true
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : null
- ObjectiveID: 9905_0059_InMemoriam
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9910_0059_d_00_container_InMemoriam
  NpcDestinationId: 9928_MSQ_YonasMemorial
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_59
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_58
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9905_0059_InMemoriam_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_objective_title"
  Description: "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9905_0059_InMemoriam_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: null
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: true
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : null
- ObjectiveID: 9926_0101_TenaciousRose
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9926_0101_d_00_container_TenaciousRose
  NpcDestinationId: 9926_VK_AbigailRoseB
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: VarangianKnights_0101
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9926_0101_TenaciousRose_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_title"
  Description: "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: null
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: null
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : null
- ObjectiveID: 9926_0103_LostScarecrow
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 28.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9926_0103_d_00_container_LostScarecrow
  NpcDestinationId: 9930_VK_RomacBarboB
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: VarangianKnights_0103
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9926_0103_LostScarecrow_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_objective_title"
  Description: "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9926_0103_LostScarecrow_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: null
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : null
- ObjectiveID: 9932_0104_RelicReclamation
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 30.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 9932_0104_d_00_container_RelicReclamation
  NpcDestinationId: 9931_VK_Caoimhe
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: VarangianKnights_0104
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9932_0104_RelicReclamation_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_objective_title"
  Description: "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9932_0104_RelicReclamation_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: null
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: null
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : true
